voilanorbert.com 2018-09-18

# Privacy policy - Norbert

**VOILANORBERT PRIVACY POLICY**

VoilaNorbert.com, LLC ( **“VoilaNorbert”** or **“we”** ) respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This privacy policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website www.voilanorbert.com (our “ **Website** “) or through one of VoilaNorbert’s chrome extensions (collectively, “ **Services** ”), and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information. This Privacy Policy applies to VoilaNorbert’s Customers and their use of the VoilaNorbert Services as well as visitors to the Website (“Visitors”). For purposes of this privacy policy, VoilaNorbert is a data controller of your personal information (as defined below). 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by VoilaNorbert offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by VoilaNorbert or any third party. This Privacy Policy also does not apply to information collected by any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website, or websites, applications or services that are operated by other parties, including Customers (as defined below).

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website or Services. By accessing or using this Website or the Services, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website and the Services after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates

  1. **** **VoilaNorbert Services**

The Services allow VoilaNorbert’s business customers (“ **Customer** ” or “ **Customers** ”) to perform email address lookup and verification and data enrichment on sets of emails. Customers can access these services through manual entry, uploading a csv file or using our APIs.t 

  2. **** **Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**

We collect several types of information from and about Visitors of our Website, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, e-mail address, telephone number, company name, company address and billing information (“ **personal information** “); and/or
  * about your internet connection and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us; and
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details (such as your activity on our Website), session data such as IP addresses and web browser software.

VoilaNorbert does not use cookies, web beacons or other tracking technology on the Website or through the Services. In addition, Voila Norbert does not respond to Do Not Track signals. Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

  3. ******Information You Provide to Us**. 

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you voluntarily provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website or subscribing to our service. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website.
  * To provide the Services, VoilaNorbert receives and stores your personal information (“Customer Data”).

  4. **How we use your information**

VoilaNorbert uses the information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information for a variety of purposes including:

  * To provide the Services. 
  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To communicate with you about your account and the Services.
  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To troubleshoot any issues with the Website or Services. 
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

VoilaNorbert processes your personal information for the purposes identified above and the legal basis for VoilaNorbert processing this information is as follows: (i) in order to provide our Services to you, (ii) for the performance of a contract between you and us, (iii) our legitimate interests, including the proper administration of our website and business, (iv) to protect your vital interests, or (v) your consent, which you may withdraw at any time.

  5. **When VoilaNorbert discloses your information**

**General**. VoilaNorbert does not provide your personal information or any other information you provide to VoilaNorbert to any unaffiliated third parties.   
**Third Parties.** VoilaNorbert may provide your personal information or any other information you provide to VoilaNorbert to contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. 

**Stripe**. If you purchase Services through the Website , then your credit card or debit card information is provided directly to our payment service processor, Stripe, to process the payments. The payment information is transmitted via an encrypted connection directly to Stripe. Stripe uses, processes and stores your personal and payment information in accordance with Stripe’s Privacy Policy available at stripe.com/us/privacy. VoilaNorbert does not store your payment information. Stripe maintains that it is PCI compliant and you can learn more about Stripe’s security measures available at stripe.com/help/security.

**Legal Requests and Comply with State and Federal Laws.**  VoilaNorbert may release personal information or other information provided by you if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws or to respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. VoilaNorbert also reserves the right to disclose personal information or other information that VoilaNorbert believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce VoilaNorbert’s Terms of Service, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of the Website or Services, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of VoilaNorbert, its Customers or others.

**In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy.**  In the event that VoilaNorbert is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal or non-personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

  6. **** **YOUR CHOICES**

**General**. We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us and we understand that you have the right to access, correct, delete, object to and restrict our use of your personal information. We also understand that you have the right to obtain a copy of your personal information from us and to withdraw your consent of the processing of your personal information by us. You can always opt not to disclose information to VoilaNorbert, but keep in mind some information is needed in order to use our Services. You may close your account by contacting us at [support@voilanorbert.com](mailto:support@linktexting.com). Please note that some information may remain in our private records even after the closure of your account or the deletion of any information from your account as noted below. In addition, we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to any of the above requests.

**Promotional Offers from VoilaNorbert**. If you do not wish to receive marketing emails from  VoilaNorbert that promote our own products or services, you can opt-out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data or at any other time by logging into the Website and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an email stating your request to support@voilanorbert.com. If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions. This opt out does not apply to information provided to VoilaNorbert as a result of a service offering purchase, product service experience or other transactions.

**Accessing and Correcting Your Information**. You may be able to add, update, or delete information in your account by logging into your account profile page at: [https://app.voilanorbert.com/#!/settings/account ](https://app.voilanorbert.com/#!/settings/account). You may also send us an email at support@voilanorbert.com to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

You may also request a copy of your personal information that you have provided to us directly by sending an email to [support@voilanorbert.com](mailto:support@linktexting.com). We will provide you a copy of your personal information in a commonly used electronic form. 

  7. **VoilaNorbert’s commitment to data security**

VoilaNorbert uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information and Customer End User Data. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to VoilaNorbert through the Website or Services and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your information, VoilaNorbert makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of your information. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If VoilaNorbert learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. VoilaNorbert may post a notice on its website if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us by sending an email to [privacy@voilanorbert.com](mailto:support@linktexting.com).

  8. **Children’s Privacy**

Our Website and the Services are not directed to children under 13 years of age. VoilaNorbert does not knowingly collect personal information directly from children under 13 years of age without verifiable parental consent. If you are under 13 years of age, then do not use or provide any information on this Website or register on the Website, or use any of the Services. If  we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [privacy@voilanorbert.com](mailto:privacy@linktexting.com).

  9. **Data Storage and Retention**

Your personal information is stored by VoilaNorbert on the servers of its cloud-based database storage provider engaged by VoilaNorbert, located in the United States. VoilaNorbert will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you with the Services. We will delete your information within 30 days of a request by you. 

If you would like more information about VoilaNorbert’s data retention practices with respect to your data or information about deletion of your data or data portability, then please contact VoilaNorbert at [privacy@voilanorbert.com](mailto:privacy@linktexting.com). 

  10. **International Transfer of Personal Information**

VoilaNorbert is located in the United States and offers its Services from the United States. If you are located outside the United States, then you understand that your personal information is transferred, processed and stored in the United States. You understand the privacy laws of the United States may not be as protective as the privacy laws of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction. Through your continued use of the Website or the Services you consent to the transfer of your personal information to the United States.

  11. **Changes to the Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the “effective date” below. If we make any material changes in the way in which your personal information is collected, used or disclosed, then we will notify you through our website or by email before the changes take effect. If you object to any of the changes, then you can close your account by contacting us as provided below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Changes to this privacy policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

  12. **California Privacy Rights for California Residents**

California residents may request certain information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by VoilaNorbert to third parties for direct marketing purposes. As noted above, VoilaNorbert does not disclose your personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes unless you have first agreed to such disclosure. However, if you would like to make such a request, then please contact VoilaNorbert at [support@voilanorbert.com](mailto:support@linktexting.com) or at the address provided in the “How you can contact us” section below.

  13. ******How you can contact us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you can contact VoilaNorbert at [support@voilanorbert.com](mailto:support@linktexting.com). In addition, you may also contact VoilaNorbert by writing to us at:  

VoilaNorbert.com, LLC  
2313 Capulet StreetAustin, TX 78741

**Date last modified:**  This Privacy Policy was last modified on May 22, 2018.
